Finding Aid for the North American New Music Festival Sound Recordings, 1983-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Cassettes, 1983-1993, I.; Cassette 1-390
  - Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Fantasy for three pianos (1951), 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 494 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 284 Side a)
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_284asc.mp3
  - Cage, John Beatles 1962-1970, 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 495 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 284 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_284bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_284bsc.mp3
  - Wyschnegradsky, Ivan, 1893-1979 Composition, piano, op. 46 no. 1 (1961), 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 496 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 285 Side a)
    Duration: 04:53
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_285aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_285asc.mp3
  - Reich, Steve, 1936- Six pianos (1973), 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 497 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 285 Side b)
    Duration: 17:29
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_285bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_285bsc.mp3
  - Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987 Piano and voices 1 (1972), 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 498 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 286 Side a)
    Duration: 27:53
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_286aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_286asc.mp3
  - Mather, Bruce Poeme du delire, 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 499 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 286 Side b)
    Duration: 17:09
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_286bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_286bsc.mp3
  - Newman, Chris, 1958- Mistake (1990), 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 500 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 287 Side a)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_287aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_287asc.mp3
  - Schwartz, Elliott, 1936-2016 Pentagonal mobile (1975), 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 501 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 287 Side b)
    Duration: 12:57
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_287bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_287bsc.mp3
  - Finnissy, Michael Romeo and Juliet: A drowning, 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 502 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 288 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 151, April 8, 1990, 5:00 p.m.
    Performers: Michael Finnissy, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_288aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_288asc.mp3
  - Finnissy, Michael Freight train blues, 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 503 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 288 Side b)
    Duration: 02:19
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_288bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_288bsc.mp3
  - Finnissy, Michael Kemp's Morris, 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 504 Tape type: TDK_SA_90 (Box 6, Audiocassette 289 Side a)
    Duration: 45:22
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_289aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_289asc.mp3
  - Finnissy, Michael English country tunes (1977), 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 505 Tape type: TDK_SA_90 (Box 6, Audiocassette 289 Side b)
    Duration: 46:31
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_289bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_289bsc.mp3
  - Gershwin, George, 1898-1937 Swanee; arr., 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 506 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 290 Side a)
    Duration: 04:18
    Arranged by Michael Peter Finnissy; Side b is blank
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_290aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_290asc.mp3
  - Mostel, Raphael Beatles sweet, 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 507 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 291 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 152, April 8, 1990, 8:00 p.m.
    On tunes by John Lennon, Paul McCartney, and George Harrison: Here, there and everywhere; Blackbird; Hide and seek in Norwegian wood; Here comes Lucy (Here comes the sun); Not on tapes in same order as printed program
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_291aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_291asc.mp3
  - Miyake, Haruna, 1942- Yesterday, 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 508 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 291 Side b)
    Duration: 05:45
    On the tune by John Lennon and Paul McCartney; Not on tapes in same order as printed program
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_291bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_291bsc.mp3
  - Curran, Alvin S., 1938- from "Eleanor Rigby", 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 509 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 292 Side a)
    Duration: 07:05
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_292aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_292asc.mp3
  - Oliveros, Pauline, 1932-2016 Norwegian wood, 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 510 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 292 Side b)
    Duration: 04:08
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_292bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_292bsc.mp3
  - Fujieda, Mamoru "All my loving" resounded, 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 511 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 293 Side a)
    Duration: 05:47
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_293aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_293asc.mp3
  - Cage, John Beatles 1962-1970, 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 512 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 293 Side b)
    Duration: 09:45
    On the tune by John Lennon and Paul McCartney; Not on printed program
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_293bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_293bsc.mp3
  - Feldman, Barbara Monk, 1953- Michelle, 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 513 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 294 Side a)
    Duration: 03:55
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_294aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_294asc.mp3
  - Mikhashoff, Yvar, 1941-1993 Mikhachelle (A mirror for Michelle), 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 514 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 294 Side b)
    Duration: 02:20
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_294bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_294bsc.mp3
  - Matsudaira, Yoriaki And I love..., 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 515 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 295 Side a)
    Duration: 05:06
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_295aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_295asc.mp3
  - Zimmermann, Walter, 1949- When I'm eighty-four, 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 516 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 295 Side b)
    Duration: 04:37
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_295bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_295bsc.mp3
  - Stone, Carl, 1953- She said she said, 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 517 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 296 Side a)
    Duration: 03:40
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_296aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_296asc.mp3
  - Marcus, Bunita Julia, 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 518 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 296 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_296bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_296bsc.mp3
  - Garland, Peter, 1952- Goddess of liberty: "You've got to hide your love away", 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 519 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 297 Side a)
    Duration: 04:29
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_297aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_297asc.mp3
  - Rzewki, Frederic Short fantasy on "Give piece [sic] a chance", 1990-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 520 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 297 Side b)
    Duration: 06:19
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_297bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_297bsc.mp3
  - Cage, John One7, 1991-04-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 521 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 298 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 153, April 18, 1991, 4:00 p.m.
    Duration: 31:32
    Performers: Unidentified
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_298aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_298asc.mp3
  - Cage, John Europera 5. Part 1, 1991-04-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 522 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 299 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 154, April 18, 1991, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 31:16
    Performers: Martha Herr, soprano; Gary Burgess, tenor; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; Jan Williams, victrola; Donald Metz, sound; Andrew Culver, director
    World premiere; Commissioned by the North American New Music Festival and De Ijsbreker
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_299aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_299asc.mp3
  - Cage, John Europera 5. Part 2, 1991-04-18, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 522 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 299 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_299bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_299bsc.mp3
  - Trawick, Eleanor, 1965- Chamber piece number 2, 1991-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 523 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 300 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 156, April 19, 1991, 11:00 p.m.
    Calumet Art Café (Buffalo, N.Y.)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_300aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_300asc.mp3
  - Dawson, Ted, 1951- Portraits of a landscape, 1991-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 524 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 300 Side b)
    Duration: 20:15
    Different work than stated on printed program
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_300bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_300bsc.mp3
  - Valverde, Gabriel, 1957- Contuan, 1991-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 525 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 301 Side a)
    Duration: 15:42
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_301aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_301asc.mp3
  - Hammer, Vincent, 1963- Blooming sketch pad, 1991-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 526 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 301 Side b)
    Duration: 15:57
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_301bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_301bsc.mp3
  - Dunleavy, Houston, 1962- Duet for two, 1991-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 527 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 302 Side a)
    Not on tape in same order as printed program
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_302aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_302asc.mp3
  - Gibson, Steve, 1962- Fissures, 1991-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 528 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 302 Side b)
    Duration: 12:16
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_302bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_302bsc.mp3
  - Patton, Christopher E., 1972- Lecture/Demonstration/Concert with video harp. Part 1, 1991-04-20, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 529 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 303 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 157, April 20, 1991, 1:00 p.m.
    Duration: 31:08
    Performers: Chris Patton
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_303aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_303asc.mp3
  - Patton, Christopher E., 1972- Lecture/Demonstration/Concert with video harp. Part 2, 1991-04-20, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 529 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 303 Side b)
    Duration: 25:33
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_303bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_303bsc.mp3
  - Moog, Bob (Robert) Lecture on the Multiply sensitive keyboard. Part 1, 1991-04-20, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 530 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 304 Side a)
    Performers: Robert A. Moog, lecturer
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_304aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_304asc.mp3
  - Moog, Bob (Robert) Lecture on the Multiply sensitive keyboard. Part 2, 1991-04-20, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 530 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 304 Side b)
    Duration: 19:48
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_304bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_304bsc.mp3
  - Widoff, Antony Insular, 1991-04-20, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 531 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 305 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 158, April 20, 1991, 8:30 p.m.
    Duration: 10:56
    Performers: Composer with MIDI electronics
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_305aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_305asc.mp3
  - Myska, David B. (David Bernard), 1955- Celebration, 1991-04-20, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 532 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 305 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_305bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_305bsc.mp3
  - Otto, Peter, 1951- Kineses vehicle, 1991-04-20, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 533 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 306 Side a)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_306aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_306asc.mp3
  - Bidlack, Rick, 1958- Six simple chaoids, 1991-04-20, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 534 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 306 Side b)
    Duration: 14:00
    Two were played: Beauty and Perpetuum; Not on tape in same order as printed program
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_306bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_306bsc.mp3
  - Chadabe, Joel Flyby, 1991-04-20, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 535 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 307 Side a)
    Performers: Jan Williams, percussion; MIDI electronics
    Side b is blank; Not on tape in same order as printed program
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_307aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_307asc.mp3
  - Tavener, John Three surrealist songs, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 536 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 308 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 160, April 21, 1991, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 11:55
    Performers: Jane's Minstrels
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_308aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_308asc.mp3
  - Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987 For Franz Kline, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 537 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 308 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_308bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_308bsc.mp3
  - Casken, John la Orana, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 538 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 309 Side a)
    Duration: 16:53
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_309aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_309asc.mp3
  - Cardew, Cornelius Octet, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 539 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 309 Side b)
    Duration: 13:17
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_309bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_309bsc.mp3
  - Weir, Judith Don't let that horse, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 540 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 310 Side a)
    Duration: 02:33
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_310aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_310asc.mp3
  - Fox, Christopher Taylor, 1962- Synchromy in orange, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 541 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 310 Side b)
    Duration: 10:58
    U.S. premiere. This could be Christopher Fox, born 1955.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_310bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_310bsc.mp3
  - Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987 De Kooning, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 542 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 311 Side a)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_311aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_311asc.mp3
  - King, Matthew M., 1959- Masters of art on the line, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 543 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 311 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_311bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_311bsc.mp3
  - Gordon, Michael, 1956- Paint it Black, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 544 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 312 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 159, April 21, 1991, 5:00 p.m.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_312aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_312asc.mp3
  - Tenney, James Beast, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 545 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 312 Side b)
    Duration: 08:22
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_312bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_312bsc.mp3
  - Hatzis, Christos, 1953- Birth of Venus, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 546 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 313 Side a)
    Duration: 19:46
    Performers: Tape; Robert Black, contrabass
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_313aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_313asc.mp3
  - Cage, John Composed improvisation for Steinberger bass guitar and snare drum, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 547 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 313 Side b)
    Duration: 09:16
    Performers: Robert Black, Steinberger bass guitar; Jan Williams, percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_313bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_313bsc.mp3
  - Druckman, Jacob, 1928-1996 Valentine (1969), 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 548 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 314 Side a)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_314aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_314asc.mp3
  - Schloss, Myrna Frances Bassist out of the landscape, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 549 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 314 Side b)
    Duration: 12:07
    Performers: Robert Black, electric bass
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_314bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_314bsc.mp3
  - Wolff, Christian, 1934- Preludes, piano, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 550 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 315 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 161, April 21, 1991, 8:00 p.m.
    Preceded by remarks
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_315aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_315asc.mp3
  - Wolff, Christian, 1934- Rosas, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 551 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 315 Side b)
    Performers: Haydee Schvartz, piano; Patti Cudd, percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_315bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_315bsc.mp3
  - Wolff, Christian, 1934- Exercise no. 26 (Snare drum peace march), 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 552 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 316 Side a)
    Duration: 03:47
    Performers: Patti Cudd, snare drum
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_316aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_316asc.mp3
  - Wolff, Christian, 1934- For Morty, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 553 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 316 Side b)
    Duration: 05:33
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_316bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_316bsc.mp3
  - Wolff, Christian, 1934- Prelude, piano, no. 5, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 554 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 317 Side a)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_317aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_317asc.mp3
  - Wolff, Christian, 1934- Look she said, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 555 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 317 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_317bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_317bsc.mp3
  - Wolff, Christian, 1934- Exercise no. 27 (2nd snare drum peace march), 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 556 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 318 Side a)
    Duration: 03:45
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_318aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_318asc.mp3
  - Wolff, Christian, 1934- Emma, 1991-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 557 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 318 Side b)
    Performers: Beverly Smith, viola; Paul Kellett, violoncello; Dominic Saunders, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_318bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_318bsc.mp3
  - Vigeland, Nils Songs in unknown tongues (1991), 1991-04-22, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 558 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 319 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 162, April 22, 1991, 12:10 p.m.
    Performers: Martha Herr, soprano; Yvar Mikhashoff, celesta; Amy Williams, piano; Jan Williams, percussion
    World premiere; Not stated on printed program
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_319aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_319asc.mp3
  - Mikhashoff, Yvar, 1941-1993 Beggars' songs (1969), 1991-04-22, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 559 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 319 Side b)
    Performers: Martha Herr, soprano; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_319bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_319bsc.mp3
  - Williams, Amy, 1969- Three songs (1991), 1991-04-22, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 560 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 320 Side a)
    Duration: 09:21
    Performers: Martha Herr, soprano; Amy Williams, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_320aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_320asc.mp3
  - Sahl, Michael, 1934- Last elms of Bidwell Parkway (1991), 1991-04-22, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 561 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 320 Side b)
    Duration: 14:41
    Performers: Amy Williams, celesta; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; Jan Williams, percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_320bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_320bsc.mp3
  - Payne, Anthony Evening land, 1991-04-22, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 562 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 6, Audiocassette 321 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 163, April 22, 1991, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 20:31
    Not same work or order as stated on printed program